Mobius, Inc. Records MS208
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Project files, 1975 -- 2005; MS208.004; 21.6 Linear Feet
  - Jo Sandman, 1986 -- 1987; MS208.004.018.00041 (Box 18)
  - Performance Art Panel -- press packet originals, 1986 -- 1987; MS208.004.018.00042 (Box 18)
  - Perf Art Panel I & II, 1986 -- 1987; MS208.004.018.00043 (Box 18)
  - CANCELLED -- Diane Arvanites, 1987; MS208.004.018.00044 (Box 18)
  - Deborah Kruger, 1983 -- 1985; MS208.004.018.00045 (Box 18)
  - West of Myself -- Mark Grodberg + Susie K., 1987; MS208.004.018.00046 (Box 18)
  - Social Terrorism, Brooks/Chipman, 1987; MS208.004.018.00047 (Box 18)
  - A Night of Video -- Mario-Erik Paoli, Michael Burlingame, 1987; MS208.004.018.00048 (Box 18)
  - Works in Progress #23, 1987; MS208.004.018.00049 (Box 18)
  - Not Defining Performance Art, 1987; MS208.004.018.00050 (Box 18)
  - Science Projects, 1987; MS208.004.018.00051 (Box 18)
  - Student Works, 1989; MS208.004.019.00001 (Box 19)
  - Tom Janzen, 1989; MS208.004.019.00002 (Box 19)
  - David Marquis, 1989; MS208.004.019.00003 (Box 19)
  - Sherry Steiner, 1989; MS208.004.019.00004 (Box 19)
  - Parlor/Yanqui, 1989; MS208.004.019.00005 (Box 19)
  - Osborn, Band, Speare +, 1989; MS208.004.019.00006 (Box 19)
  - Fireworks as Perf, 1989; MS208.004.019.00007 (Box 19)
  - Grandma's Quilt, 1989; MS208.004.019.00008 (Box 19)
  - Roof Dance, 1989; MS208.004.019.00009 (Box 19)
  - Artist Index and Newsletters, 1989 -- 1990; MS208.004.019.00010 (Box 19)
  - Evening w/o Music, Joanne Rice/Lisa Wilcox, 1989; MS208.004.019.00011 (Box 19)
  - Orly Azran, 1989; MS208.004.019.00012 (Box 19)
  - Of Tanne, 1989; MS208.004.019.00013 (Box 19)
  - Intnl Arts Exchange STUMPF, 1989; MS208.004.019.00014 (Box 19)
  - Consequences of Simple Moving, deLahunta, 1989; MS208.004.019.00015 (Box 19)
  - Morgan/Korteweg, 1989; MS208.004.019.00016 (Box 19)
  - Open Studios, 1989; MS208.004.019.00017 (Box 19)
  - Dinosaur Duet (Julie Rochlin + Victor Young), 1989; MS208.004.019.00018 (Box 19)
  - PARLOR -- Nancy Adams, 1989; MS208.004.019.00019 (Box 19)
  - Works-in-Progress #29, 1989; MS208.004.019.00020 (Box 19)
  - Thomas/Witham, 1989; MS208.004.019.00021 (Box 19)
  - AIDS Quilt, 1989; MS208.004.019.00022 (Box 19)
  - Exact Location/Dead Leaves, 1989; MS208.004.019.00023 (Box 19)
  - Visual Aids, 1989; MS208.004.019.00024 (Box 19)
  - Visual Aids, 1989; MS208.004.019.00025 (Box 19)
  - Discussion, 1990; MS208.004.019.00026 (Box 19)
  - Johny Blood, 1990; MS208.004.019.00027 (Box 19)
  - Mari + Dan -- The Big Game, 1990; MS208.004.019.00028 (Box 19)
  - Dreams of Home & the Beginning or the End, 1990; MS208.004.019.00029 (Box 19)
  - Dreams of Home, 1990; MS208.004.019.00030 (Box 19)
  - Kathy Marmor, 1990; MS208.004.019.00031 (Box 19)
  - Artrages 13th B-Day Party, 1990; MS208.004.019.00032 (Box 19)
  - W.I.P. #30, 1990; MS208.004.019.00033 (Box 19)
  - Bart Uchida: Half Past..., 1990; MS208.004.019.00034 (Box 19)
  - David Keevil, 1990; MS208.004.019.00035 (Box 19)
  - Mobile Monads, Finkelpearl, Adams, 1990; MS208.004.019.00036 (Box 19)
  - Student Verks, 1990; MS208.004.019.00037 (Box 19)
  - Bridging the Gap, 1990; MS208.004.019.00038 (Box 19)
  - Eric Hughes, 2000; MS208.004.019.00039 (Box 19)
  - Ed Osborn, 1990; MS208.004.019.00040 (Box 19)
  - Odd Dance, 1990; MS208.004.019.00041 (Box 19)
  - Burlington Exchange, 1990; MS208.004.019.00042 (Box 19)
  - Bonner/Domandi HAIR Project, 1990; MS208.004.019.00043 (Box 19)
  - P + H, 1990; MS208.004.019.00044 (Box 19)
  - P + H, 1990; MS208.004.019.00045 (Box 19)
  - WIP #31, 1990; MS208.004.019.00046 (Box 19)
  - Laura Knott Dance Co., 1990; MS208.004.019.00047 (Box 19)
  - Laura Liverman, 1990; MS208.004.019.00048 (Box 19)
  - Connolly, M. June Cow Sea Bride, 1990; MS208.004.019.00049 (Box 19)
  - Volunteers/Interns, 1990 -- 1991; MS208.004.019.00050 (Box 19)
  - Season Rejection Letters, 1990 -- 1991; MS208.004.019.00051 (Box 19)
  - Day Without Art, 1990; MS208.004.019.00052 (Box 19)
  - Hannah Goodwin, Collection of Dreams, 1990; MS208.004.019.00053 (Box 19)
  - Sharon Brody: A Day Without Art/Female Artists Against AIDS, 1989; MS208.004.019.00054 (Box 19)
  - Thomas E. Janzen, 1990; MS208.004.019.00055 (Box 19)
  - Chrysalis/Joanne Rice, Dog Days/Nolan + N. Jones, 1990; MS208.004.019.00056 (Box 19)
  - Jeff Krieger, 1990; MS208.004.019.00057 (Box 19)
  - Persona -- Mathew Meneri, 1990; MS208.004.019.00058 (Box 19)
  - T-N-T, 1990; MS208.004.019.00059 (Box 19)
  - Open Studios, 1990; MS208.004.019.00060 (Box 19)
  - Scott deLahunta -- Movement Workshop, 1990; MS208.004.019.00061 (Box 19)
  - Of Tanne/Joan Gale, 1990; MS208.004.019.00062 (Box 19)
  - LeBrun/Hickles, 1990; MS208.004.019.00063 (Box 19)
  - Sexagenery, 1990; MS208.004.020.00001 (Box 20)
  - Month of Blood + Bonfires, 1990; MS208.004.020.00002 (Box 20)
  - Dolls: Dziedzic, 1991; MS208.004.020.00003 (Box 20)
  - Emile Tobenfeld, 1991; MS208.004.020.00004 (Box 20)
  - Coitus/Kathy Marmor, 1991; MS208.004.020.00005 (Box 20)
  - Student Works, 1991; MS208.004.020.00006 (Box 20)
  - Mary Tsiongas, 1991; MS208.004.020.00007 (Box 20)
  - Frank Vasello, 1991; MS208.004.020.00008 (Box 20)
  - Counting Her Dresses, Home Street Home, 1991; MS208.004.020.00009 (Box 20)
  - Calitlin Corbett, 1991; MS208.004.020.00010 (Box 20)
  - Linda Graetz, 1990; MS208.004.020.00011 (Box 20)
  - Movement WIP, 1991; MS208.004.020.00012 (Box 20)
  - Taylor McLean, 1991; MS208.004.020.00013 (Box 20)
  - K. Johnson et al, 1991; MS208.004.020.00014 (Box 20)
  - P+H, 1991; MS208.004.020.00015 (Box 20)
  - Brayton/Evans DADA, 1991; MS208.004.020.00016 (Box 20)
  - Taylor McLean, 1991; MS208.004.020.00017 (Box 20)
  - Fido Rodenbeck, 1991; MS208.004.020.00018 (Box 20)
  - David MacLean, 1991; MS208.004.020.00019 (Box 20)
  - Robert Goss, 1991; MS208.004.020.00020 (Box 20)
  - Last Days of Mankind, Pay Americana, BCFE, 1991; MS208.004.020.00021 (Box 20)
  - Nathan Hemenway, 1991; MS208.004.020.00022 (Box 20)
  - Patricia McCabe, Who Will Rule What?, 1990; MS208.004.020.00023 (Box 20)
  - Artist Index, 1991 -- 1992; MS208.004.020.00024 (Box 20)
  - Marcella Correa, 1991; MS208.004.020.00025 (Box 20)
  - Meg Cottam, 1991; MS208.004.020.00026 (Box 20)
  - Mark Pugh, Caerdroia, 1991; MS208.004.020.00027 (Box 20)
  - Hannah Bonner -- Inside Out, 1991; MS208.004.020.00028 (Box 20)
  - Lois Folstein, 1991; MS208.004.020.00029 (Box 20)
  - Music w/o Pants, Ean White, Clam Thtr, 1991; MS208.004.020.00030 (Box 20)
  - Open Studios, 1991; MS208.004.020.00031 (Box 20)
  - Pat Murphy, 1991; MS208.004.020.00032 (Box 20)
  - Ricardo Frota, 1991; MS208.004.020.00033 (Box 20)
  - Kaye Lynn Johnson, 1991; MS208.004.020.00034 (Box 20)
  - Month of B&B Jones, White, Nolan, 1991; MS208.004.020.00035 (Box 20)
  - Joan Silver, 1991; MS208.004.020.00036 (Box 20)
  - Taylor McLean -- 5 Headed Monster + Angelic Possession, 1991; MS208.004.020.00037 (Box 20)
  - Joseph Wilson, 1991; MS208.004.020.00038 (Box 20)
  - ARTrages On!, 1991; MS208.004.020.00039 (Box 20)
  - Day W/out Art/Kitchen Project, 1991; MS208.004.020.00040 (Box 20)
  - Taylor McLean, 1991; MS208.004.020.00041 (Box 20)
  - Counting Her Dresses, David Miller, 1991; MS208.004.020.00042 (Box 20)
  - Time Spent At Home, Nancy Adams, Marilyn Arsem + Joanne Rice, 1991; MS208.004.020.00043 (Box 20)
  - Tim Martin, Dance Theatre Consort, 1992; MS208.004.020.00044 (Box 20)
  - Jack-n-Jill Bad Boy o' Art Blasphemy Mucho, 1991 -- 1992; MS208.004.020.00045 (Box 20)
  - Guadulesa/Joly Keys of Infinity, 1992; MS208.004.020.00046 (Box 20)
  - Pugh/Brown "Authorities", 1992; MS208.004.020.00047 (Box 20)
  - 88 Room, 1992; MS208.004.020.00048 (Box 20)
  - Dennis Downey, Full Moon Confucius, 1992; MS208.004.020.00049 (Box 20)
  - Persephone + Hades, 1992; MS208.004.020.00050 (Box 20)
  - Party Hive!, 1992; MS208.004.020.00051 (Box 20)
  - Fork, Knife, Spoon, Nancy Adams, 1992; MS208.004.020.00052 (Box 20)
  - Talking About Something Else/Parables + Parabolas, Taylor McLean, 1992; MS208.004.020.00053 (Box 20)
  - Malcolm Goldstein, Bartuchica + Marsem, 1992; MS208.004.020.00054 (Box 20)
  - Apprehension of Fire, Ean White, 1992; MS208.004.020.00055 (Box 20)
  - DIG, Sarah Hickler, Elizabeth Witham, 1992; MS208.004.020.00056 (Box 20)
  - Volunteers, 1991 -- 1992; MS208.004.020.00057 (Box 20)
  - Counting Her Dresses, 1992; MS208.004.020.00058 (Box 20)
  - W.I.P., 1992; MS208.004.020.00059 (Box 20)
  - NH/UT Composers Cultivating the Verve, 1992; MS208.004.020.00060 (Box 20)
  - Stirring, Spinning, Sweeping, 1992; MS208.004.020.00061 (Box 20)
  - Visum et Repastum, Man Novotny-Jones, Cathy Nolan, Ean White, 1992 -- 1994; MS208.004.020.00062 (Box 20)
  - Student Works, 1992; MS208.004.020.00063 (Box 20)
  - Student Works, 1992; MS208.004.020.00064 (Box 20)
  - Heaven/Hell, 1992; MS208.004.020.00065 (Box 20)
  - Masashi Harada, 1992; MS208.004.020.00066 (Box 20)
  - Piece for April, Tom Plsek, larry Johnson, Joanne Rice, 1992; MS208.004.020.00067 (Box 20)
  - Ann Scott, 1992; MS208.004.020.00068 (Box 20)
  - Marianne Connolly, 1992; MS208.004.020.00069 (Box 20)
  - Susie Nacco/Beth Gaurilles, 1992; MS208.004.020.00070 (Box 20)
  - Landon Rose/Bill Gilbert, 1992; MS208.004.020.00071 (Box 20)
  - WIP #32, 1990; MS208.004.020.00072 (Box 20)
  - Artist Index and Newsletters, 1992 -- 1993; MS208.004.021.00001 (Box 21)
  - Volunteers, 1992 -- 1993; MS208.004.021.00002 (Box 21)
  - Charles Coe, 1991; MS208.004.021.00003 (Box 21)
  - The Freedom of Expression, H.S. art project, Charles Coe, 1992; MS208.004.021.00004 (Box 21)
  - Lois Folstein, 1992; MS208.004.021.00005 (Box 21)
  - Hannah Dennison, 1992; MS208.004.021.00006 (Box 21)
  - MAG Sampler, 1992; MS208.004.021.00007 (Box 21)
  - New Music Across America, 1992; MS208.004.021.00008 (Box 21)
  - James Williams "Park City", 1992; MS208.004.021.00009 (Box 21)
  - BCFE events, 1992; MS208.004.021.00010 (Box 21)
  - Darla Villani, 1992; MS208.004.021.00011 (Box 21)
  - Joe Briganti, 1992; MS208.004.021.00012 (Box 21)
  - FPAC Open Studios, 1992; MS208.004.021.00013 (Box 21)
  - Tom Plsek, 1992; MS208.004.021.00014 (Box 21)
  - Dworin X-Charge, 1992; MS208.004.021.00015 (Box 21)
  - Artrages, 1992; MS208.004.021.00016 (Box 21)
  - Day Without Art, 1992; MS208.004.021.00017 (Box 21)
  - Stirring Spinning Sweeping, 1992; MS208.004.021.00018 (Box 21)
  - Ean White, 1992; MS208.004.021.00019 (Box 21)
  - Linda Graetz, 1992; MS208.004.021.00020 (Box 21)
  - Frank Vasello -- Cloister, 1993; MS208.004.021.00021 (Box 21)
  - Mary Trev Warren, 1993; MS208.004.021.00022 (Box 21)
  - Lewis Gesner, 1993; MS208.004.021.00023 (Box 21)
  - Neil Leonard, 1993; MS208.004.021.00024 (Box 21)
  - WIP #33, 1993; MS208.004.021.00025 (Box 21)
  - Raqib Hassan, 1993; MS208.004.021.00026 (Box 21)
  - Ross Barron, 1992; MS208.004.021.00027 (Box 21)
  - Andrew Neumann, 1993; MS208.004.021.00028 (Box 21)
  - Wallace/Burns, 1993; MS208.004.021.00029 (Box 21)
  - HS -- FOE, 1993; MS208.004.021.00030 (Box 21)
  - HS FOE Project, 1993; MS208.004.021.00031 (Box 21)
  - Student Works, 1993; MS208.004.021.00032 (Box 21)
  - David Fuqua/Degeneration Series, 1993; MS208.004.021.00033 (Box 21)
  - Cage Project, 1993; MS208.004.021.00034 (Box 21)
  - Tittemore, 1993; MS208.004.021.00035 (Box 21)
  - Movement WIP, 1993; MS208.004.021.00036 (Box 21)
  - CANCELLED -- Ann Scott/The Stations, 1993; MS208.004.021.00037 (Box 21)
  - Resurrection Engine, Ean White, 1993; MS208.004.021.00038 (Box 21)
  - M. Arsem Stirring, Spinning, Sweeping, 1993; MS208.004.021.00039 (Box 21)
  - Gary Duehr, 1993; MS208.004.021.00040 (Box 21)
  - P + H, 1993; MS208.004.021.00041 (Box 21)
  - Art Rages, 1993; MS208.004.021.00042 (Box 21)
  - Ellen Band, 1993; MS208.004.021.00043 (Box 21)
  - Pam Wunderlich, Glamour Animal Series, 1993; MS208.004.021.00044 (Box 21)
  - Taylor McLean, 1993; MS208.004.021.00045 (Box 21)
  - David Miller/Stein Piece, 1993; MS208.004.021.00046 (Box 21)
  - CANCELLED -- Apprehension of Fire, Ean White, 1993; MS208.004.021.00047 (Box 21)
  - Kristin Johnson, 1993; MS208.004.021.00048 (Box 21)
  - Artist Index and Newsletters, 1993 -- 1994; MS208.004.022.00001 (Box 22)
  - Volunteers, 1993 -- 1994; MS208.004.022.00002 (Box 22)
  - Resist, 1993; MS208.004.022.00003 (Box 22)
  - Ann Scott, 1993; MS208.004.022.00004 (Box 22)
  - Nancy Adams, 1993; MS208.004.022.00005 (Box 22)
  - Marilyn Arsem, 1993; MS208.004.022.00006 (Box 22)
  - White Neamann, 1993; MS208.004.022.00007 (Box 22)
  - Events/Scheduling, 1993 -- 1994; MS208.004.022.00008 (Box 22)
  - Proposal Rejections Fall '93, 1993; MS208.004.022.00009 (Box 22)
  - CANCELLED -- Ann Scott, Dream Circle/Harvest, 1993; MS208.004.022.00010 (Box 22)
  - Bob Walthall, 1993; MS208.004.022.00011 (Box 22)
  - Fall Sampler, 1993; MS208.004.022.00012 (Box 22)
  - Ellen Anthony, 1993; MS208.004.022.00013 (Box 22)
  - Open Studios, 1993; MS208.004.022.00014 (Box 22)
  - Poetry FR, 1993; MS208.004.022.00015 (Box 22)
  - Tom Plsek, 1993; MS208.004.022.00016 (Box 22)
  - Nancy Rider, 1993; MS208.004.022.00017 (Box 22)
  - Taylor McLean, 1993; MS208.004.022.00018 (Box 22)
  - Ean White, 1993; MS208.004.022.00019 (Box 22)
  - Meredith Dans, 1993; MS208.004.022.00020 (Box 22)
  - Movement WIP, 1993; MS208.004.022.00021 (Box 22)
  - WIP #34, 1993; MS208.004.022.00022 (Box 22)
  - Day W/Out Art, 1993; MS208.004.022.00023 (Box 22)
  - Margaret Titlemore, 1994; MS208.004.022.00024 (Box 22)
  - Judy Dworin, 1994; MS208.004.022.00025 (Box 22)
  - Landon Rose, 1994; MS208.004.022.00026 (Box 22)
  - Ron Wallace, 1994; MS208.004.022.00027 (Box 22)
  - Betsy Whirlabout, Deep Space Dancers, 1994; MS208.004.022.00028 (Box 22)
  - Panel - Performance from Boston, 1994; MS208.004.022.00029 (Box 22)
  - Jeff Becker/Malcolm McClay CRISUS, 1994; MS208.004.022.00030 (Box 22)
  - Student Works, 1994; MS208.004.022.00031 (Box 22)
  - Tom Plsek, "Outsider Music", 1993 -- 1994; MS208.004.022.00032 (Box 22)
  - Red in Woods -- Marilyn Arsem, 1994; MS208.004.022.00033 (Box 22)
  - Full Moon Gruel, Billinger, Jones + Jones, 1994; MS208.004.022.00034 (Box 22)
  - Hickler Here/Not Here, 1994; MS208.004.022.00035 (Box 22)
  - Erika Batdorf, 1994; MS208.004.022.00036 (Box 22)
  - HSFCE, 1994; MS208.004.022.00037 (Box 22)
  - Dreams of Forgotten Alchemists, Mari N.-J., 1994; MS208.004.022.00038 (Box 22)
  - Nora Valdez, 1994; MS208.004.022.00039 (Box 22)
  - Joe Wilson PIGS FEET, 1994; MS208.004.022.00040 (Box 22)
  - WIP #35, 1994; MS208.004.022.00041 (Box 22)
  - Persephone + Hades, 1994; MS208.004.022.00042 (Box 22)
  - "This is Art, This is Not Art" Linda Graetz, 1994; MS208.004.022.00043 (Box 22)
  - Under the Red Sun, Taylor McLean, 1994; MS208.004.022.00044 (Box 22)
  - Caroline Bagenal, 1994; MS208.004.022.00045 (Box 22)
  - James Williams, 1994; MS208.004.022.00046 (Box 22)
  - Survival Dances, Dance Complex, 1994; MS208.004.022.00047 (Box 22)
  - Movement + Construction, 1994; MS208.004.022.00048 (Box 22)
  - Susan White, 1994; MS208.004.022.00049 (Box 22)
  - Artist Index, 1999 -- 2000; MS208.004.022.00050 (Box 22)
  - General Fall '00 / +NL Spring '01, 2000 -- 2001; MS208.004.022.00051 (Box 22)
  - Rejection Letters, 2001; MS208.004.022.00052 (Box 22)
  - Proposal Review Letters, 2000; MS208.004.022.00053 (Box 22)
  - Proposals, 2000; MS208.004.022.00054 (Box 22)
  - Faculty Revu, Open FauceT, 2000; MS208.004.022.00055 (Box 22)
  - Report from Afield: Living Myth Project, Mari Novotny-Jones, Diane Edgecomb, Ean White, 2000; MS208.004.022.00056 (Box 22)
  - Multi-Media Performance Ensemble Interface, 2000; MS208.004.022.00057 (Box 22)
  - Charros de Video, VideoSpace, 2000; MS208.004.022.00058 (Box 22)
  - Everyday, Jeff Huckleberry, 2000; MS208.004.022.00059 (Box 22)
  - Wanderlust, Mark Lepson, 2000; MS208.004.022.00060 (Box 22)
  - Disrobe/Redress Stephen Sheffield/Gina Cestaro, 2000; MS208.004.022.00061 (Box 22)
  - Baggage, Marjorie Morgan, 2000; MS208.004.022.00062 (Box 22)
  - Means Mainly Become: Realization Method Mac Low, David Miller, 2000; MS208.004.022.00063 (Box 22)
  - Vestigial House, Harriett Jastremsky, 2000; MS208.004.022.00064 (Box 22)
  - No Talent And So No Sin Performance Troupe, 2000; MS208.004.022.00065 (Box 22)
  - Report from Afield, Invisible Cities Group, 2000; MS208.004.022.00066 (Box 22)
  - Artificial Life VideoSpace, 2000; MS208.004.022.00067 (Box 22)
  - Root, Water -- Nest Bird, Boston-Macedonia Collaborative Project, 2000; MS208.004.022.00068 (Box 22)
  - Flying and Flowing, Milan Kohout, David Franklin, 2000; MS208.004.023.00001 (Box 23)
  - Perform the Making of Object, Yin Peet, 2000; MS208.004.023.00002 (Box 23)
  - Mobius Sampler, MAG & Open Stad, 2000; MS208.004.023.00003 (Box 23)
  - Paci'dello/Bardoni, Bible Belt Tour, "Gynomite", 2000; MS208.004.023.00004 (Box 23)
  - Report from Afield: Recent work in Germany, Marilyn Arsem, 2000; MS208.004.023.00005 (Box 23)
  - Virtual Motion, David Rodwin also workshops, 2000; MS208.004.023.00006 (Box 23)
  - Noh TV VideoSpace, 2000; MS208.004.023.00007 (Box 23)
  - Ripe, Julia Szabo, 2000; MS208.004.023.00008 (Box 23)
  - Neither Out Far Nor In Deep, Jennifer Hicks, 2000; MS208.004.023.00009 (Box 23)
  - Finding Roma, 2000; MS208.004.023.00010 (Box 23)
  - Report from Afield: Who Owns the Homeland, Milan Kohout, 2000; MS208.004.023.00011 (Box 23)
  - The Crazed Animated Genius of Ben Jones, VideoSpace, 2000; MS208.004.023.00012 (Box 23)
  - Work-in-Progress #44, 2000; MS208.004.023.00013 (Box 23)
  - Report from Afield: Civil War in Sudan, Khalid Kodi, 2001; MS208.004.023.00014 (Box 23)
  - Les Anges Gardiens, Diane Landry, 2001; MS208.004.023.00015 (Box 23)
  - Maternal Exposure, Monica Bock, 2001; MS208.004.023.00016 (Box 23)
  - Reports from Afield: Looking Inside, 2001; MS208.004.023.00017 (Box 23)
  - The Learning Mirror, Shawn Gurzak, 2001; MS208.004.023.00018 (Box 23)
  - Straight from the Source, Youth Perspectives, 2001; MS208.004.023.00019 (Box 23)
  - Neovoxer: art is the new god., 2001; MS208.004.023.00020 (Box 23)
  - Hanged Man's Love, Theater Vigoda, 2001; MS208.004.023.00021 (Box 23)
  - Translating: Denmark to Boston, 2001; MS208.004.023.00022 (Box 23)
  - Radio PU -- Open FauceT -- Ross Hamlin, 2001; MS208.004.023.00023 (Box 23)
  - Reports from Afield: Touchable Stories Series, 2001; MS208.004.023.00024 (Box 23)
  - Relative Distance, Jacqueline Goss, 2001; MS208.004.023.00025 (Box 23)
  - Student Works, 2001; MS208.004.023.00026 (Box 23)
  - Domestic Archeology, Site/Insite, 2000; MS208.004.023.00027 (Box 23)
  - Peregrinations, Tom Plsek + Marjorie Morgan, 2001; MS208.004.023.00028 (Box 23)
  - Reports from Afield: art colonies in the balkans, 2001; MS208.004.023.00029 (Box 23)
  - Scavenger Hunt II: Open FauceT, 2001; MS208.004.023.00030 (Box 23)
  - Movement Works-in-Progress #10, 1999 -- 2000; MS208.004.023.00031 (Box 23)
  - Movement Works in Progress, 2001; MS208.004.023.00032 (Box 23)
  - iEar@Mobius R.P.I. integrated electronic arts, 2001; MS208.004.023.00033 (Box 23)
  - Lerman/Moss VideoSpace, 2000; MS208.004.023.00034 (Box 23)
  - Imaging New England, Margaret Wagner, et al & General Fest info, 2001; MS208.004.023.00035 (Box 23)
  - Drawing by Chance, 2001; MS208.004.023.00036 (Box 23)
  - Water/Rice, 2001; MS208.004.023.00037 (Box 23)
  - Reports from Afield, 2000 -- 2001; MS208.004.023.00038 (Box 23)
  - Political Info -- Waterfront, Southie, etc., 2000 -- 2001; MS208.004.023.00039 (Box 23)
  - Stark: J. Hicks, 2001; MS208.004.023.00040 (Box 23)
  - Reports from Afield: Glorious Subversion, 2001; MS208.004.023.00041 (Box 23)
  - Teens Show VII, 2001; MS208.004.023.00042 (Box 23)
  - Multi-Instrumental Solo, 2001; MS208.004.023.00043 (Box 23)
  - My 5 Year Old Daughter, 2001; MS208.004.023.00044 (Box 23)
  - Ferrous City Cavedogs, 2001; MS208.004.023.00045 (Box 23)
  - Tibor's Wedding, 2001; MS208.004.023.00046 (Box 23)
  - Thresholds, 2001; MS208.004.023.00047 (Box 23)
  - Submergence, 2001; MS208.004.023.00048 (Box 23)
  - Reports from Afield: Choreographing the Consciousness, 2001; MS208.004.023.00049 (Box 23)
  - The Third Room, 2001; MS208.004.023.00050 (Box 23)
  - Spring, 2002; MS208.004.024.00001 (Box 24)
  - Path of the Mystic, 2001; MS208.004.024.00002 (Box 24)
  - The Erik Satie Cabaret, 2001; MS208.004.024.00003 (Box 24)
  - Theatre Fest, 2001; MS208.004.024.00004 (Box 24)
  - Reports from Afield, 2001; MS208.004.024.00005 (Box 24)
  - This is a Test, 2001; MS208.004.024.00006 (Box 24)
  - Radio Pu, 2001; MS208.004.024.00007 (Box 24)
  - Weeping Wall, 2001; MS208.004.024.00008 (Box 24)
  - VideoSpace, 2001; MS208.004.024.00009 (Box 24)
  - The How-To Dances, 2001; MS208.004.024.00010 (Box 24)
  - Mobius Artists Group Show, 2001; MS208.004.024.00011 (Box 24)
  - CONGLOMOCO Employee Appreciation Night, 2001; MS208.004.024.00012 (Box 24)
  - Shed, 2001; MS208.004.024.00013 (Box 24)
  - Reports from Afield: Chinatown Banquet, 2001; MS208.004.024.00014 (Box 24)
  - Not Frida in Ode (to a planet Dying Young), 2001; MS208.004.024.00015 (Box 24)
  - Art Installation + Design UNNI, 2001; MS208.004.024.00016 (Box 24)
  - Monkey House, 2001; MS208.004.024.00017 (Box 24)
  - VideoSpace present Noise/Performance/Video, 2001; MS208.004.024.00018 (Box 24)
  - Art Rages, 2001; MS208.004.024.00019 (Box 24)
  - Reports from Afield: Trance Dance, 2001; MS208.004.024.00020 (Box 24)
  - Peter Schumann, 2001; MS208.004.024.00021 (Box 24)
  - Body Tales for the New Millenium, 2001; MS208.004.024.00022 (Box 24)
  - One String of MU: Oneness = Nothingness, 2001; MS208.004.024.00023 (Box 24)
  - Babel Part Four: Redemption, 2001; MS208.004.024.00024 (Box 24)
  - Ferrous City, 2001; MS208.004.024.00025 (Box 24)
  - Works in Progress #14, 2001; MS208.004.024.00026 (Box 24)
  - Reports from Afield: Mobius Zadar Exchange, 2001; MS208.004.024.00027 (Box 24)
  - Press, 2001; MS208.004.024.00028 (Box 24)
  - Public Art Series Misc., 2001; MS208.004.024.00029 (Box 24)
  - Public Art Permits, 2001; MS208.004.024.00030 (Box 24)
  - Anne Lilly, 2001; MS208.004.024.00031 (Box 24)
  - Mitch Rosenberg, 2001; MS208.004.024.00032 (Box 24)
  - Bill Reyelt, 2001; MS208.004.024.00033 (Box 24)
  - Public Art Series, 2001; MS208.004.024.00034 (Box 24)
  - Adams/Sokolovski, 2001; MS208.004.024.00035 (Box 24)
  - Tyrrell/Vieira, 2001; MS208.004.024.00036 (Box 24)
  - Bill Diveney, 2001; MS208.004.024.00037 (Box 24)
  - Lisa Greenfield, 2001; MS208.004.024.00038 (Box 24)
  - Don Eyles, 2001; MS208.004.024.00039 (Box 24)
  - Persephone: Descent of Flowers, 2002; MS208.004.024.00040 (Box 24)
  - Body Stories, 2002; MS208.004.024.00041 (Box 24)
  - Reports from Afield: 25 Years of the African, 2002; MS208.004.024.00042 (Box 24)
  - Green, 2002; MS208.004.024.00043 (Box 24)
  - Mirror Project, 2002; MS208.004.024.00044 (Box 24)
  - R.F.A.: William Pope L., 2002; MS208.004.024.00045 (Box 24)
  - AAMARP 25, 2002; MS208.004.024.00046 (Box 24)
  - Puppet Underground, 2002; MS208.004.024.00047 (Box 24)
  - R.F.A.: "Human Lives", 2002; MS208.004.024.00048 (Box 24)
  - Videoarchaeology, 2001; MS208.004.024.00049 (Box 24)
  - R.F.A.: Joan Jonas, 2002; MS208.004.024.00050 (Box 24)
  - Student Works, 2002; MS208.004.024.00051 (Box 24)
  - Student Works, 2001; MS208.004.024.00052 (Box 24)
  - Student Works, 2001; MS208.004.024.00053 (Box 24)
  - Mutlidisciplinary Charrette, 2002; MS208.004.024.00054 (Box 24)
  - Katsura Kan, 2002; MS208.004.024.00055 (Box 24)
  - Variations V, 2002; MS208.004.024.00056 (Box 24)
  - Zadar, 2001; MS208.004.024.00057 (Box 24)
  - Public Art Series, 2001; MS208.004.024.00058 (Box 24)
  - Press Releases, 2001; MS208.004.024.00059 (Box 24)
  - Mediating the Channel (1 of 2), 2002; MS208.004.024.00060 (Box 24)
  - Mediating the Channel (2 of 2), 2002; MS208.004.024.00061 (Box 24)
  - Margaret Tittemore -- art is like food, 2001; MS208.004.024.00062 (Box 24)